How to create 1 lecture from 0 doidão?
I'll get 1 coin.
If I give you a face,
I tell you,
if I give a crown,
I won't talk,
it will be a surprise
crown I told you which TDH is fire bro I said that this EU tale I'm going
to tell you mano caraca mano and then 1 company saw that I gave a lecture
and was very interested it needs a lecture with a theme
on how you use narrative for sales,
for this type of sale you make,
you can.
But I didn't tell them that I don't have the lecture if it called,
I'm going to have to create a lecture here from zero to zero,
let's go,
how I can differentiate myself from the other speakers
who sometimes have 1 good story,
but it communicates badly,
sometimes you communicate well,
but a bad story deconstructs something interesting.
First I need to understand what I want to say
and then put together the presentation.
If I do it backwards,
man,
you're traveling in layout.
Don't leave the place
how does she look like the new one?
I need to present the project first to see if the guys there,
all over the world trying to fit inside 1 box
and few people thinking outside of it.
Hope the person tastes bro
until tomorrow.